原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译:  glida    euniceluo   zoeyyyyy    加热闪电饺子
翻译:  冰蓝    洗七里   赌性坚强赛太公
校对:  统统打入冷宫赛
时间轴:  三水
后期:  瓜瓜    总监： 怀念浓子的瓜瓜
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    美剧炸了
了解最新影视资讯字幕信息
摩  登
家  庭
第八季 第十六集
最新海外影视剧下载
你确定我们需要加这么多冰吗  儿子
Are you sure we need that much ice, buddy?
所有美国职篮球员都用冷水浸浴法
All NBA players use cold water immersion therapy.
运动后泡20分钟能缓解肌肉酸痛与疲劳感
来吧
Let's do it.
你说得对  也没那么...
You're right. It's not that b--
一年前的今天  我有机会成为英雄
One year ago today, I had the chance to be a hero.
那是年度高中慈善篮球比赛
It was the annual high school charity basketball game --
家长对战老师
parents versus teachers.
我们在为出勤率办公室的马丁太太筹钱
We were raising money for Mrs. Martin in the attendance office
泥石流冲垮了她的房子
who lost her house in a mudslide.
房子前一分钟还"出席"  下一分钟就"缺席"了
One minute it was present, the next it was absent.
我们落后两分  比赛只剩一秒钟  我来罚球
Down 2, a second left, I was fouled.
胜负就在我手中
The game was in my hands.
在巨大的压力之下  我掉链子了
I crumbled under the pressure.
这赎罪的机会我等了一年
I've waited a year for my shot at redemption
这次我不要留任何弱点
and left nothing to chance.
下手重点
Harder!
我像疯子一样锻炼
I have worked out like a madman --
传球运球训练  敏捷训练
passing and dribbling drills, agility training...
最厉害的是  我每天练习100个罚球
...and I top it all off with 100 free throws every day...
23.
24.
无论我那天有多累
...no matter how tired I am.
85.
我经历了一年的痛苦训练  但我已经准备好了
It had been a year of painful training, but I was ready.
我把果汁洒在地毯上了  请别告诉妈妈
I spilled juice on the rug. Please don't tell Mama.
别告诉妈妈
Don't tell Mama?
怎么不说别告诉爸爸
What about "Don't tell Papa?"
男孩应该害怕自己的父亲
A boy is supposed to fear his father.
在我爸爸身边  我瑟瑟发抖
I shook in my boots around my old man,
他在他爸爸身边也是如此
just like he did around his.
直到今天  我听见打开施丽兹啤酒的声音
To this day, I hear the crack of a Schlitz
或者闻到辛格尔顿须后水的味道时
or smell some Singleton's Beard Tonic,
都会像小意大利区的黑帮叛徒一样浑身出汗
and I'm sweating like a mob rat in Little Italy.
我绊倒了
Ow! Oh, tripped!
够了
Enough!
要我跟你说多少次你才会捡起你的玩具
How many times have I told you to pick up your toys?
你真搞笑
You're funny!
够了  捡起玩具
Enough! Pick up the toys!
歌洛莉亚  真是惊喜
Gloria! What a surprise!
曼尼的学校有个妈妈
There's a mom at Manny's school
我跟她不太对盘
that I've had some problems with.
她就是典型的金发傻帽芭比娃娃医生
She's your typical blonde airhead Barbie doll doctor.
你好啊  唐娜
Hola, Donna.
你是不小心逛到这里来了吗
Did you wander in by mistake?
这里可不卖鞋
You know they don't sell shoes here.
天啊  你买这么多热狗
Oh, no, I see you buy a lot of hot dogs.
你就这样放弃保持身材真是太惨了
It's so sad when someone just gives up.
我要在高中慈善篮球赛上卖这些
I'm selling these at the high school charity basketball game.
可怜的马丁太太
Poor Mrs. Martin.
今年我们要为她筹钱换肾
This year we're raising money to get her a new kidney
我们能指望你吗
So, can we count on you?
捐肾吗
For the kidney?
写张捐款支票  就跟你以前一样
To write a check, like you always do.
行啊
Yes.
捐钱几乎算得上和做实事一样好呢
Money is almost as good as actually doing something.
房地产拍卖会上40美元买的  你敢信吗
$40 at the estate sale? Can you believe that?
你根本不会发现是拍卖品
Like, there's no way you'd even notice.
爸爸  好啊
Dad, hi.
打开12频道
Turn on channel 12.
新闻曝光了一种
It's an expose on cheap lumber
内含致人生病的化学制品的廉价木材
that's got some chemical in it that's making people sick,
"衣柜衣柜衣柜衣柜"公司买了许多
and Closets, Closets, Closets, Closets bought a bunch of it.
瞧瞧  是厄尔的女儿雪莉
Oh, look -- There's Earl's daughter, Shirl.
抓到你了
我们采访了这位
We caught with the local man
与受污染的木材接触之后
who reported flu-like symptoms
出现了类流感症状的当地男子
after contact with the tainted wood.
我只是想给我妻子做一个
I just wanted to give my wife
跟她一样美丽的衣柜
a closet as beautiful as she is.
我们不是买了一些...
Didn't we buy some of --
你能相信厄尔的蠢货女儿
Can you believe Earl's dum-dum daughter
从那些笨蛋手里买了木材吗
bought wood from those bozos?
当然啦  你俩长大时
Of course, when you two were growing up,
她一直都是比较笨的那个
she was always the slow one.
你记得她把那气球当她朋友吗
You remember when she thought that balloon was her friend?
气球达·卡莱尔
Balloon-da Carlisle.
好吧  我继续忙了  爸爸
Right. Well, back to it, Dad.
回头见
See you later.
我就知道那木头这么划算  肯定有鬼
I knew that deal was too good to be true.
现在我看起来就要跟一个
And now I'm gonna look as stupid as a girl
把班里的两只兔子都抚摸死的女孩一样蠢了
who pet two different class rabbits to death.
喝点茶吗  先生
A spot of tea, sir?
是上等的我就喝
Only if it's the fancy kind.
我的天
Oh, my God.
我们的英音都变得这么熟练了
How good have our accents gotten?
-太不可思议了  -是啊
- It's insane. - Yeah.
海莉4岁的时候  我们办了第一次茶话会
When Haley was 4, she and I had our first tea party,
从那以后  我们把茶话会变成了传统
and since then, we've made it a tradition
每年都一起喝一次下午茶
to meet for high tea once a year.
我真的很珍惜这些时光
It's a time I've really come to cherish.
我不喜欢他们这个什么茶话会
I don't love the whole tea thing.
米奇尔和海莉总是分享秘密
Mitchell and Haley always come back giggling
说说笑笑地回来  我觉得我被排挤在外
over shared secrets, and I feel left out.
我试过自己搞一个舅舅侄女传统活动  但
I once tried to start my own uncle-niece tradition, but...
我不是质疑加速质谱法
I'm not questioning the methodology
背后的方法论
behind accelerated mass spectrometry.
我只是单纯指出不是只有这个方法
I'm merely pointing out that it's not singular
才能够从丰度高的其他同位素中
in its power to separate a rare isotope
分离出稀有的同位素
from an abundant neighboring mass.
你和那个帅气的天气预报员交往得怎么样
What's going on with you and that handsome weatherman?
大部分时候都很好
Things are great, mostly.
挺好的
Yeah.
"大部分时候"
Oh. "mostly"?
遇到什么问题了吗
Well, what's-what's going on?
你能接受你的伴侣
I mean, do you think it's okay for your partner
对你提出的任何要求吗
to ask you to do... anything?
不能  不是任何要求都能接受
Mm, no. Not anything anything.
我们都有个人界限
I mean, we all have our boundaries.
还是有些事是我不会叫小卡去做的
I mean, there are still things I wouldn't ask Cam to do.
好吧  是这样的  某天晚上
Okay. So, um, Rainer and I
雷纳和我躺在床上  然后...
were in bed the other night, and...
然后怎么
And?
他叫我做某件
He asked me to do something
让我有点不舒服的事
I'm not totally comfortable with.
他叫你做什么了
What'd he ask you to do?
我不会评头论足的  你准备好了再说
No-No judgments. Just whenever you're ready.
他当时侧躺着
So, he was lying on his side,
他说要以那种体位才能做
and he said that that was part of it,
然后他叫我c...
and then he asked me to c-
海莉
Haley!
他叫你做什么
What'd he ask you to do?
快  写在这张餐巾纸上
Quick, write it down on this napkin.
雷纳  你怎么来了
Rainer, what are you doing here?
你把耳机落在我车里了
You left your earbuds in my car.
我知道你喜欢以它们为借口来无视别人
I know you like to use them to ignore people.
你想和我们一起喝茶吗
Do you want to join us?
-你不介意吧  米奇舅舅  -怎么会
- You don't mind, do you, Uncle Mitch? - No!
老大姐在看着你  肾脏
回到这里的感觉太奇怪了
It feels weird to be back here.
我曾败在这间体育馆里
This gym got the better of me once.
爸  你又要把自己逼疯了
Dad, you're psyching yourself out.
你说得对
You're right.
今年与去年唯一的区别
The only thing different between this year and last
是今年我有备而来
is I'm prepared this year.
德安德鲁·乔丹和查尔斯·巴克利也来了
And DeAndre Jordan and Charles Barkley are here.
这里是往手上盖已买票章的地方吗
Is this where we get our hand stamped?
有时候我喜欢去别的地方逛逛再回来
Sometimes I like to leave and come back to things.
你们怎么来了
Uh, why-why are you here?
我们经纪人的妻子是这所学校的数学老师
Our agent's wife is a math teacher at the school.
咱去占座吧
Let's go get our seats.
我们不想被人们挡住视线
We don't want anybody to block us.
是啊  我懂
Yeah, yeah. I-I get that.
所以我得在大牌职篮球星面前打球吗
So, I'm playing in front of two NBA stars?
还有  一旦人们听说他们在这
Plus, once people know they're here,
围观群众肯定会比去年多五倍
the crowd will be like five times the size it was last year.
消防局长不会让这么多人挤在馆里的
Well, we still live in a world with a fire marshal.
等等
Wait.
没准他们只是来露个脸
They're probably just here to show their faces
站个台就走了
and make a quick exit...
爸  别被他们影响
Dad, don't let them faze you.
你为此艰苦训练过
This is what you've trained for.
你准备好了
You're ready.
你说得对
You're right.
我只要放松一下就好了
I just need to shake the jitters off a little bit.
交给我  拉里
I got you, Larry.
定点跳投
Spot up.
不
No!
歌洛莉亚  真的是你吗
Gloria? Is that you?
我的大脑不能接受你出现在此情此景里
My brain's having a hard time processing you in this context.
我来卖玉米片筹善款
Yeah, I came to sell my nachos to raise money.
你人真好
How nice.
尽管有人说你的努力来得太迟太少
Although, some people are saying it's too little too late,
你不能来露个脸就指望能记上一功
that you can't just show up and get credit for it.
我觉得这些话很刻薄
I think it's mean,
但有些人说你看起来有点虚伪
but some people are saying it seems disingenuous.
我刚到这
I just got here.
你是什么时候听这些人说这些话的
When did you talk to all these people?
我认为你会发现这些人
I think you'll find this crowd
不宣[喜欢]玉米片
no lika da nachos.
如果你觉得学口音很种族歧视  我感到抱歉
I'm sorry if that sounds racist.
才没有呢
No, it didn't.
我根本就没听出你在取笑哪种语言
I don't even know what language you were trying to make fun of.
既然你不打算走  你可以在那支个摊
Okay, since you're not leaving, you can set up down there.
不
No.
那好黑  还很偏
It's very dark, and it's very far away!
祝你好运
Good luck!
看起来我发的咱仨的合照
Looks like that picture I Instagrammed of the three of us
挺受我粉丝欢迎呢
is a big hit with Rainer Nation.
你就这么发定位安全吗
And is it safe to post your location like that?
你难道不担心有人跟踪你
Aren't you worried about stalkers?
不会  没事的
Oh, no, it's fine.
我的大多数粉丝
Most of my followers
都是些过度兴奋  极端缺爱的老女人
are just overly excited, love-starved old ladies.
你们的独家茶话会对外开放了啊
Oh, I see your exclusive tea party opened up.
他才刚发推特
He just posted that.
你是在餐厅外兜圈等待吗
What, are you circling the restaurant?
你好  雷纳·向恩
Hey, Rainer Shine.
感恩节的时候你就坐他旁边
You sat next to him at Thanksgiving.
对对  曼尼  快坐  一起啊
Right! Manny! Sit down. Join us.
小卡  咱俩能单独聊会儿吗
Actually, Cam, could I talk to you for a second?
雷纳来之前
Okay, before Rainer walked in,
海莉正要说雷纳让她做的
Haley was about to tell me something upsetting
在床上某件令她感到略不舒服的事
he asked her to do in the bedroom.
我没听到太多  他让她...
Now, I didn't get much, but he asked her to c--
什么
To what?
他让她...
He asked her to c--
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding me?
都不要再靠近我俩了  谢谢合作
Okay, no one else come near us. Thank you.
她就说了个c  然后雷纳就闯进来了
That's all she got out -- "C--." And then Rainer walked in.
我们必须得问清楚
Well, we have to find out.
作为她的舅舅  我们要掌握尽多的情况
As her uncles, we need all the information we can
这样才能更好地给她作指导啊
so we can advise her properly.
没错  她约会对象比她大好多
Yeah. She's dating an older man.
如果她不舒服  咱们有责任保护她
If she's uncomfortable, it's our duty to protect her.
好  那咱们达成一致
Okay. So we said all that.
c开头的词都有啥啊
What could "C--" be?
-萝卜  -不对
-Carrot? -Mnh-mnh.
杯吸法
Cupping?
你不会觉得是加拿大长跳吧
You don't think it could be a Canadian long jump, do you?
这招里并没有需要女人的地方啊
What part would a woman play in that?
这是最后一份文件线索
That's the last of the paper trail.
干得漂亮
Great.
这个地图上的红别针标的
Okay, and so the red pins on this map mark
是有毒木材制成的衣柜
all the locations of closets
所发往的地点
that were made with the toxic wood.
我们已经召回了
Okay, and we have recalled
十个里我们已经召回九个了
9 out of 10 of the contaminated closets,
我们只需追踪剩下的最后一个
so we only have to track down one more.
既然你没问  绿色别针
And since you didn't ask, the green pins
是我所有的潜在父亲的住址
are all the addresses of potential fathers of mine.
你们在干嘛呢
Oh, hey. How're you doing?
我听说有人没登记就用了我的粉碎机
Did I hear somebody using my shredder without signing it out?
没
No.
碎纸屑
Confetti!!
那孩子完全不怕我
Hey! The kid doesn't fear me as he should,
所以我把他带到这
so I brought him in here
让他看看我霸道总裁的一面
to show him my scary boss side.
-配合点  -好的
-Play along. -Okay.
本  你觉得我是有多傻
Ben, how dumb do you think I am?
你发现了吗
You found out?
我当然发现了  我啥都知道
Of course I found out. I know everything.
全是她的主意
It was her idea!
-本  -不  他做得很好
-Ben! -No, he's doing great.
你惹上大麻烦了  小子
You're in big trouble, mister.
杰  真的对不起  我们正要尽力
Jay, I'm so sorry. We were just trying to s--
够了
Enough!
我们走  乔
Come on, Joe!
够了
Enough!
你招供速度还能再更快点吗
Could you have rolled over any faster?
我爸啥都不知道
My dad didn't know anything.
这只是为了他小孩演的戏
That was just a big act for his kid.
我知道  我只是配合演出
Yeah, I know. I was playing along to --
得了吧
Save it, okay?
绿色别针指的某个地方  有个很失望的老爸
Somewhere, one of these green pins is very disappointed.
玉米片  来点玉米片吧
Nachos. Come get some nachos.
根本没人知道我在后面
No one even knew that I was back there.
当你连我声音都听不到时  就知道有多吵了
You know it's loud when you can't hear my voice!
天啊
My goodness.
照这样  我要打破自己的销售记录了
At this rate, I'll break my own sales record.
你们好  想来点玉米片不
Hola. Do you guys want to try some nachos?
听起来不错啊
That sounds pretty good.
你的贼心也太一目了然了  格伦
Ugh, you are so transparent, Glenn.
快来  快来
Come, come, come.
本店扩张开始卖薯片了
We're expanding to chips.
小卡  你太明显在盯着人家了
Cam, you're staring.
我才没有  你不也是
No, I'm not. So are you.
我得接电话  可能跟雨情有关
Ohh, I should take this. It might be drizzle-related.
海莉  我们是来鼓励你说出c...是什么的
So, Haley, we are here to help you tell us what "C--" is.
你竟然告诉他了
You told him?
你可以放心倾诉  我们是中年同性恋
You can confide in us. We're middle-aged gay men.
不管是什么  我们肯定都听说过
Whatever it is, we have heard of it.
好吧
Fine.
某天晚上  雷纳问我
The other night, Rainer asked me
是否愿意做
if I would be into
耳烛
candling.
你们知道那是什么吧
You know what that is, right?
-当然  -当然
- Yes! - Yes!
就是做那个...
It's when you do the...
然后  然后...
and then -- and then you --
然后再噗噗
and then you do the -- the boop, boop.
耳烛就是点燃一根中空的蜡烛放入...
Candling is where you light a hollow candle and insert it...
一边耳道内
into one of the ear canals...
以清除耳垢
to remove ear wax.
老天
Ah -- oh, God.
问题是  我不知道自己是否
The thing is, I don't know if I want to be
想和雷纳那么亲密
that intimate with Rainer.
我真的准备好看到他流出的耳屎了吗
Am I really ready to see gunk coming out of his ear?
万一看完觉得他不性感了怎么办
I mean, like, what if he stops being sexy?
就是这样的亲密事
Well, it is intimacy like that
才能让人分出随便谈谈与真爱的不同
that separates casual dating from something more serious.
那你之前说的呢
But what about what you said earlier,
即使你们这么坚定的伴侣也有个人界限
how even committed relationships like yours have boundaries?
说什么  什么界限
Excuse me, what boundaries?
我手机没电了  能借用你们的吗
Hey, my phone died. Can I borrow one of yours?
你跟她说我们有界限吗
You told her we have boundaries?
你跟他们说我让你给我做耳烛吗
You told them I asked you to candle me?
我感觉我们快喝不了茶了
Okay, I feel like this tea's getting away from us.
玉米片  来买玉米片啊
Nachos! Get your nachos here!
走开
Get!
干扰球  裁判  吹哨啊
Goaltending! Ref, do your job!
我只是个药剂师
I'm a pharmacist.
抱歉
Oh, sorry.
菲尔
Phil.
你似乎有点紧绷
You seem a little tight, man.
德安德鲁·乔丹
Hey, DeAndre Jordan.
没有没有  只是稍稍有点怯场
Uh, no, no, no, just working out the jim-jams.
反正前半重在了解对手
First half's about getting a read.
好吧
Yeah, right.
我都不知道粉丝还能指导呢
I didn't realize that fans were coaching.
而且你帮的是家长队
And you're helping the parents.
教师是我们国家的支柱
Teachers are the backbone of our country.
滚吧
Get out of here.
当父母是这世上最艰难的工作
Parenting is the hardest job in the world.
我受够了你自作聪明的样子
I'm so sick of you acting like you know everything.
你去看心理医生真是屁用都没有
Going to therapy did nothing for you.
首先  你别转队了
First of all, stop transferring.
曾有过一场违背口头协议的转队闹剧
其次  不如我指导那支队伍
Secondly, how about I coach that team,
你指导这支队伍
you coach this team?
10块海豚币赌你和菲尔输定了
10 Dolphin Dollars you and Phil are going down.
10块连个泡棉海豚都买不起
10? You can't even get a Foam Flipper with that.
何不赌50海豚币
Let's make it 50.
德哥  别这样
D.J., please.
50块现金怎么样
How bout 50 real ones?
好  那就5000美金
Okay. Make it five grand.
一下抬这么高吗
That's the jump?
为我赢下这场
Go win this for me.
好
Okay.
我们是同一队的
We're on the same team!
犯规  有人对我犯规
Foul! Somebody fouled me!
别假摔了
Stop flopping!
菲尔  加油  专注点
Phil, come on, man. Focus!
我们刚赌上了奥运金牌
We just bet our Olympic gold medals.
为什么  没人逼你做到这一步
Why? No one's making you do this!
我不想让你不自在
I hate that I made you uncomfortable.
我只是想让我们对彼此更真实
I-I just wanted us to be real with each other.
我也想这样
I want that, too.
我准备好了  我会给你做耳烛
I think I'm ready. I will candle you.
瞧瞧
Oh, look at that --
两个真实的陌生人打破隔阂
two virtual strangers breaking down walls
而我原先都不知道我们有隔阂
when I didn't even know we had any.
我告诉海莉我们有界限
When I told Haley we had boundaries,
只是指某些事
I just meant that there are certain things
我不会想请你做
I'd rather not ask you to do.
比如呢
Like what?
不管我们有何需求
We should be open and honest
都该对彼此坦诚
about whatever our wants and needs are.
既然我们决定坦诚以对
As long as we're being real,
我有件事要向你坦白
there's something you need to know.
我什么事情都愿意...
There is absolutely nothing I --
别打扰我看好戏
Shh! I want to hear this.
把你的手给我
Give me your hands.
好  深呼吸  海莉加油
Okay, deep breath. Come on, Haley.
我的眉毛是画出来的
I draw in my eyebrows.
素颜的我长这样
This is the real me.
他吓跑了吗  他还在不在
Did he leave? Is he still here?
我还在  而你还是一样的美丽动人
I'm still here, and you're still beautiful.
别再逃避我了
Stop running from me.
好吧
Fine.
我也有件事要向你坦白
I have a confession of my own.
看完好戏再说
Two seconds.
我从来没告诉过任何人
I've never told anyone this.
我用胶带给脖子拉皮
I use tape to pull my neck back.
我就知道
I knew it!
好帅好勇敢
Wow. So brave.
我现在感觉好赤裸
I feel so naked right now.
我也是
Me, too.
他们看起来根本没差别  是不
They look exactly the same, right?
有差  他们看起来很幸福
No, what they look is happy
因为他们勇敢地
because they are brave enough
-向对方展现了自己脆弱的一面  -小卡
- to be vulnerable with each other. - Cam --
你知道有多讽刺吗  你不敢叫我
It's just ironic that you won't ask me
帮你做那件神秘的事
to do whatever it is
因为你怕我会评判你
because you're worried I'll judge you,
然而我现在就在评判你  因为你不信任我
but I'm judging you now for not trusting me,
这样真的很伤人
and that hurts.
你说得果然没错
You're right, of course.
这样做真的使我们的关系更亲密了
This is only bringing us closer together.
当然啦  平时是找谁帮你弄来着
Uh-huh! Who'd you say normally does this?
我以前办公室附近的一家店
Uh, this place near my old office.
万不得已时也会找莉莉
Lily in a pinch.
好啦  应该刮干净了
Okay, well, I think that's it.
不行  你还要再刮一遍
Oh, no, you have to go over it one more time.
够了  又不是在给桥上漆
Okay, we're not painting a bridge.
我已经找了两遍了
Okay, I've checked twice.
都没找到最后一个毒衣柜的发票
There's no invoice for this last closet.
肯定有的
Well, there has to be,
一定要找出来  不能被我爸看到
and we've got to find it before my dad does.
会不会是你不小心放碎纸机里碎掉了
Is there any chance you accidentally shredded it?
淡定  就算真的碎掉了  我也能轻易拼回来
Don't worry. If I did, it's an easy restore.
我可是地区拼图大赛60岁以下组别的冠军
I was regional jigsaw champion in the under-60 category.
这诡异的喷嚏
That weird sneeze.
听着就跟新闻上那个得病男的症状一样
You sound like the guy who was sick on the news.
怎么会  那人都快要散架了
No, that guy was falling apart.
你不可能被感染了
You can't be infected.
你并没有跟那块木板接触过
It's not like you've spent any time around that wood.
你又不会去仓库
I mean, you don't hang out in the warehouse.
-我见识过他们有多爱脱你裤子整你  -天啊
- I've seen how much those guys pants you. - Oh, my God.
我妈妈交了个新男友
My mom has a new boyfriend,
她不想让他知道她有孩子
and she doesn't want him to know she has kids,
所以每次他来我家  我就要到会议室过夜
so when he comes over, I sleep in the conference room.
会议室里有个样板衣柜
Which is where the sample closet is,
难怪找不到销售记录
which is why there's no record of it!
天啊
Oh, God!
我不常自夸这一点
I don't like to talk about it a lot,
可是我对木材挺有研究
but I have a certain expertise in timber.
即使蒙上眼睛
Even blindfolded,
我也能区分得出加拉帕戈斯柚木和马耳他樱木
I can tell a Galapagos teak from a Maltese cherry.
有一次还用上了这个技能
Came in handy for a cop friend of mine.
帮我的警察朋友逮捕了《雪松兄弟》
Helped him round up the Cedar Boys.
《雪松兄弟》是一部澳洲犯罪电影
爸
Dad? Hey!
你进来这里干吗
What are you doing in here, huh?
我在检查这块新木
I'm checking out this new wood.
那才不是新木呢
It's not new wood.
他有什么毛病啊
The hell's the matter with him?
他过敏啦
He's got allergies. Yeah.
我过敏  是过敏
Allergies. Allergies.
爸  你看到我们
Oh, Dad, have you -- have you seen
新买的鱼缸没
this new fish tank we just got?
瞧瞧多漂亮
Check it.
你之前说这木材是从哪里进货的
Where did you say we got this wood?
拜托  这破木头有什么好研究的
Please, stop obsessing about the wood.
-这鱼好像饿鬼投胎一样  -就是啊
- Hungry little sucker, huh? - Oh, yeah.
他吃掉这木头真的没问题吗
You sure that's okay for him to eat?
没问题啊
Yeah, it's fine.
那种鱼就是以生命力顽强著名的
Those fish are celebrated for their hardiness.
坚韧不拔
Yeah, hardy.
他们在饶舌歌手圈里很受欢迎
Yeah, they're very popular amongst rappers
因为在按摩浴缸和香槟里都能养活
'cause they do equally well in Jacuzzis and champagne.
乔在哪里
Where's Joe?
-跟玛格丽特在一起  -好吧
- He's with Margaret. - Oh, okay.
我去带他过来  给他看看这个鱼
I'm gonna bring him in here, have him check out this fish.
-好主意啊  -继续说这木头
-That's a good idea. -Getting back to this wood.
爸  这木头没问题  是...
Dad, the wood is fine. It's --
天...
Oh, my --
结果发现  这木头不止会让人病
Turns out, the wood doesn't just make people sick.
还会弄死鱼
It also kills fish.
我不敢让我爸知道我买了杀鱼木
Well, I couldn't let Dad know I bought murder wood,
所以我让本下楼去
so I sent Ben to get a replacement fish
从大堂鱼缸弄只一样的鱼来
from the tank in the lobby.
看起来还不错吧
So, those seem right to you? Hmm?
质量结实
They're strudy enough.
转轴平滑
Smooth pivot.
抽屉平高
Even glide.
我本来就对这木头有疑心  它还杀了鱼
I was already suspicious of that wood, but then it kills fish?
克莱尔绝对是买到了受污染木头
Claire obviously bought some of that tainted lumber,
她还想瞒着我
and then she tries hide it?
她心里一定觉得我比美国黄松木还傻[结实]
She must think I'm denser than a Ponderosa maple.
用起来感觉又好又顺手啊
That's a nice, easy ride.
对啊
Yeah.
闺女  你的手为什么湿了
Hey, kiddo, why's your hand wet?
不是啦  是流手汗而已
It's not. It's sweaty.
我今天早上去健身了
I went to the gym this morning.
周五练腿练手
Fridays I do legs and hands.
克莱尔  你让我去弄的水
Claire, here's the water you asked for.
谢谢
Thank you!
我牙都掉了
My tooth just fell out.
我喉咙好像卡了点什么
You know, I got a little something stuck in my throat.
这水让我喝一口
Give me a slug of that water.
你不会想喝这个大堂水的
Oh, no, you don't want this lobby water.
我就喝一小口就行
I just need a sip.
是从大堂饮水机装来的
It's from the fountain,
仓库工人喝的时候嘴都会贴上去
and the warehouse guys put their mouth all over it.
给我就是了
Just give it to me.
不行
I can't.
天啊  你还真喝下去了
Oh, my God, you actually did it.
能感觉到那玩意在你肚子里游吗
Can you feel that thing swimming around in your belly?
你知道里面有鱼的啊
You knew there was a fish in there?
我看见你把原来那只扔掉了
I saw you toss the other one out.
你就这么怕犯错我发现
You're so afraid of getting caught screwing up,
你宁愿吞下一只生物吗
you'd swallow an animal?
感觉你们谈家事需要空间
This sort of seems like a family thing,
而且我的视线开始狭窄了...
and my vision is tunneling, so...
好吧  用了那批木头的产品已经召回
All right, well, we recalled all the bad wood,
但这并不代表我们没犯错
but that doesn't mean that we didn't screw up.
所以你来吧  好好骂我一顿吧
So, go ahead, let me have it.
手撕你闺女
Tear my head off.
说我这次又怎么让你失望了
Tell me how I've disappointed you yet again.
这是怎么回事
And what is happening?
今天一天我都在想办法让乔怕我
All day long I've been trying to get Joe to fear me.
但或许这对孩子并不好
Maybe that's not the best thing for kids.
辛辣可口玉米片
你来啦
Hi.
我赚了六块海豚币
Well, I made six Dolphin Dollars
还有某个怪人给我20块真钞
plus 20 real ones from some weirdo
让我直接舀一勺起司进他嘴里
who wanted me to ladle cheese straight into his mouth.
好吧  乖儿子谢谢你帮忙
All right, papi, thank you so much,
但我还是需要人帮忙吸引客人来我摊子
but I still need help attracting customers over there.
我可以去菲尔的车上看看
Oh, I can see if Phil has that thing in his car
他那个会这么挥舞的东西
that flails around like this.
卡莱尔吗
Claire?
不是啦  是空气跳舞男
No, his Tube Dude.
有何能为您效劳吗
Can I help you with anything?
我想要用我最后五块海豚币买个零食
I'm just going to buy a snack with my last five Dolphin Dollars.
我不想把这个丢掉
I don't want to throw them away.
证据就是这么留下的
That's how they get you.
玉米片特别好吃
The nachos are amazing.
但绝对别去
But do not get anything
那边那摊子买东西
from the stand that is over there --
那个热狗女士吗
The hot dog lady?
她刚才也这么说了你
She just said the same thing about you.
你们两个让我想起我跟德安德鲁·乔丹
You two remind me of me and DeAndre Jordan.
我们是宿敌  我也不知道为什么
We have a rivalry, and I don't know why.
或许我们在生活中  就讨厌着拿着镜子
Maybe in life we resent people who hold up a mirror
逼我们看到自己最丑恶一面的人
and force us to look at the worst in ourselves.
我听懂你意思了  查尔斯·巴克利
I see what you're saying, Charles Barkley.
我们打篮球的把这叫助攻
And that's what we call an assist.
买过票盖过章了
Hand stamp.
唐娜  我们不能再斗下去了
Donna, we have to stop this fighting.
有位智者曾告诉过我  我们讨厌
A wise man once told me that we resent mirrors
让我们看到自己丑恶一面的镜子
that show us what we don't want to see.
真是可笑
That's ridiculous.
我可喜欢镜子了
I love mirrors.
但重点是我生气是因为
But the point is that I was mad
你让我看清了我真实的一面
because you made me see who I really am,
而我对自己变成的模样感到讶异
and I was shocked to see what I have become.
别说了
Stop talking.
你的话听起来好有人味  我不喜欢这样
You're sounding human, and I don't like that.
我集万千宠爱于一身  本以为这让我有点羞愧
I am soft, privileged lady, and I thought that bothered me.
直到今天  我才意识到压根没有
Until today, I realized that it doesn't.
我才不想辛苦来卖小吃
I don't want to do this.
我喜欢我炊金馔玉的  膏粱锦绣的生活
I love my pretty, pretty life.
而唯一让我感到不安的事
The only thing that makes me feel bad
竟然是我并不为此感到难为情
is that I don't really feel bad about it.
谢谢你愿意敞开心扉和我说这些话
Thank you so much for opening up to me.
我差一点就要对你产生一点感情了
I almost started to feel something for you,
但当你又说了你不觉得羞愧
but then when you said you don't feel guilty,
我的愤怒值又反涨了十倍
my rage returned tenfold.
而我需要这愤怒的感觉  它是我每天起床的动力
And I need that rage. It gets me up in the morning.
如果这能帮到你  从今天起我想吃什么就吃什么
Well, if it helps you, I eat everything I want,
然后大概一年就只锻炼一次
and I work out like once a year.
你这个小妖精
You're horrible.
谢谢你
Oh, thank you.
大家听好了  现在追平了  就剩下最后三秒钟
All right, guys -- tie game, three seconds left.
我们要做世上唯一一件他们意想不到的事情
There's only one thing that they're not gonna be expecting.
我们要把球传给菲尔
We're gonna get the ball to Phil.
什么?
What?
他们甚至防都不防你
They're not even guarding you.
我对这招很有信心  我跟巴克利赌上我的车了
I'm so sure of this play, I just bet Barkley my car.
是本田车吗?
Is it a Honda?
是以我头像为车头标志的劳斯莱斯幻影
No, it's a Phantom with my head as the hood ornament.
来吧  我们打赢这场比赛
All right, let's win this thing
菲儿  亲爱的  这里!
-Phil, honey, hi! -Hey.
对不起我们来迟了
I'm sorry we're late,
但好在我们及时赶来看到了比赛的结局
but at least we're here for the end of the game.
在我牛饮金鱼的日子  最需要一场胜利高兴一下
I could really use a win on the day I drank a fish.
是"鲸吸牛饮"
Drank like a fish.
天啊  一堆职篮球员在推特上聊
Wow, a bunch of NBA players are tweeting about this bet
关于巴克利和德安德鲁之间的这场赌局
between Charles Barkley and DeAndre Jordan.
而且他们还在现场直播这场比赛
And they're live-streaming it,
现在大概有六万人在线观看
so like 60,000 people are watching.
人们什么时候开始这么关心篮球了
Since when do people care about basketball?
冷静下来  菲尔  你可以做到的  哥们
Calm down, Phil. You can do this, pal.
你偏偏选这时候第一次相信我吗
You choose now to believe in me for the first time?
上场了 菲尔  你可以做到的
All right, Phil. You got this, man.
罚两球
Two shots!
我走不动了  教练
I can't go, Coach.
我的膝盖好痛
Ow! My ankle.
哎哟哟
Well, well, well...
联赛规则是这样的  如果一个队员
League rules dictate, if a player can't attempt
因为受伤不能进行罚球
a free throw because of injury,
对方球队将可以任意在罚球队选择一个投手
opposing team gets to pick the shooter.
的确  但你一样不是百事通
Right, but you're not a know-it-all.
不要给我这份愤怒的力量
Don't give this anger power.
我选你了  千万"别怯场"啊
I pick you. Don't choke.
你能行的  菲尔  你最棒了  菲尔
You got this, Phil. You got this, Phil.
菲尔·邓菲站到了罚球线前
Phil Dunphy to the free-throw line.
比数平手
Tie score.
现在是决胜时刻了  朋友们
This is for all the marbles, folks.
怎么搞的
Come on!
发生什么了
What happened?
要等一个小时他们才能把电力恢复
It's gonna take an hour to get the power back up,
所以他们就宣布平局结束
so they called the game.
我为菲尔感到好难过
I just feel so bad for Phil.
他这个重在参与  成败在天型的乐天派
You know him as this happy-go-lucky guy,
其实在心里谴责自己一整年了
but he has been beating himself up over this for a year.
而他就差一点就可以证明自己了
And he was so close!
不知道最后到底会不会进这事
It's gonna haunt him never knowing
将会在他心里不断萦绕
if he would have made that shot.
胜败就此一举
Game's on the line.
大家都在看着你
Everybody's watching.
现在是决胜时刻了  朋友们
This one's for all the marbles, folks.
这个小兔崽子居然真进了
Son of a bitch made it.
你知道  我很高兴我们能再举办一次茶话会
You know, I'm glad we're doing this again.
是啊  我感觉我们给第一次施加太大压力了
Yeah, I think we just put too much pressure on it the first time.
其实人类不是唯一一个
You know, humans aren't the only ones
会被压力带来负面影响的种族
who respond badly to pressure.
不知道我没有跟你提过无蛋日
Did I ever tell you about the day without eggs?
那发生在煎蛋节刚刚开始的时候
It was at the start of the Omelet Days Festival.
太阳一出来  我就带上我的篮子
Up with the sun, I grab my basket,
走进了鸡棚  34只母鸡  连一个蛋都没有
into the henhouse I go -- 34 hens, nary an egg.
我知道  我知道
I know, I know.
我爷爷说这是自珍珠港后他所见过
My grandpa said it was the worst case of avian anxiety
最严重的一次禽类焦虑症了
he's seen since Pearl Harbor.
所以后来他们才要把收音机从鸡棚里收走...
That's when they had to take the radio out of the coop.